Alex Zghonnyk

Address:
4066 Hinkle Lake Road, Boston,
Massachusetts
Phone:
+1 857-222-7635
Email:
alexzgonik030303@gmail.com

Summary

Infomaze is an offshore web and mobile app development company with over 16+ years' experience. Provide complete web and mobile solutions, with expertise in customized product development and service solutions including – Telecom, Hardware, Print & Signage, Business-to-Business, Home Décor, Automobiles, Health-Care, Field Service, Gaming & Casino, Real Estate, Travel & Hospitality, Education & E-Learning, Service Industry and others.

Solutions range from CRM, Workflow Management Systems, eCommerce, Ordering, B2B Solutions, Automation, Field Service, MIS, Estimating & Quote management, Job Management, Scheduling, Property Management, Accounting Systems, Application Migration, Web Services & API, Maintenance and other work.

Skill Highlights

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solver
- CRM
- Magento
- Data Scrapping
- Hybrid(Ionic & React Native)

- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused
- SalesForce
- Data Mining
- Mobile Apps(Android & iOS)

Experience

Web Developer - 09/2015 to Current

Software Outsourcing - Offshore Development, James, California

 Customized Product Development - Some Solutions are used by Telecom Giants of the US Region Content Management, eCommerce Solutions - Used by clients across the globe Application Migration - One of them is one of the biggest Service Provider in the US Region Software Maintenance.

Web Developer - 09/2015 to Current

CRM - Customization, Chris, New York

 Customized Zoho, SalesForce, Sugar CRM, Suite CRM, vTiger Customization, API, WebHook Solutions.

Web Developer - 09/2015 to Current

Database Design & Development, John, New York

• Databases were the foundation of critical IT infrastructure.

Alex Zghonnyk

Address:
4066 Hinkle Lake Road, Boston,
Massachusetts
Phone:
+1 857-222-7635
Email:
alexzgonik030303@gmail.com

• Infomaze provide end-to-end solutions for database requirement. Made it to be administration, development, deployment, maintenance or optimization Solutions.

Web Developer - 09/2015 to Current Property Software Solutions, Marcov, California

- Property Search Solution.
- Owner Records, Search.
- Comparable Sales Records.
- Lending Rates.
- Property Campaign

Education

Bachelor of Science: Computer Information Systems - 2014

Columbia University, NY